backlinksgenie.com 2012-04-15

# Backlinks Genie - Privacy Policy

BackLinksGenie Privacy Policy (Effective Date October 1, 2010 ) 

BackLinksGenie respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains BackLinksGenie Inc. ("BackLinksGenie") treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to all BackLinksGenie websites referencing this Privacy Policy (the "BackLinksGenie Sites") and all services made available on the BackLinksGenie Sites (collectively, unless noted otherwise, the "BackLinksGenie Services"). This Privacy Policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices and review and update your personal information. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites which are not owned or controlled by BackLinksGenie. 

INFORMATION COLLECTED In the course of operating the BackLinksGenie Services, we may collect two types of information about our users: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. 

"Personal Information" is personally identifiable information, such as your name, and email address. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering for a BackLinksGenie Service, such as when you choose to subscribe to a BackLinksGenie Service, enter a BackLinksGenie promotion, purchase an BackLinksGenie product, or choose to receive an BackLinksGenie newsletter. In addition, if you choose to contact any of our customer service representatives, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive Personal Information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information. 

"Non-Personal Information" is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) , the domain used to access a BackLinksGenie Service, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on a BackLinksGenie Service, is also considered Non-Personal Information. Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating the BackLinksGenie Services. For example, our Web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie when you choose to visit a BackLinksGenie Service. Non-Personal Information is used by BackLinksGenie as described here . 

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION Personal Information may be used by us for the following purposes: 

Providing you with the BackLinksGenie Services and information you have requested from us, including your use of the BackLinksGenie Sites. We may from time to time use your Personal Information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to the BackLinksGenie Services; 

If you indicated that you were interested in receiving offers or information from BackLinksGenie or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, BackLinksGenie or such sponsors or advertisers may send you email materials and other mailings about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. It is the intent of the Company to share your personal information with select third-party partners who provide targeted product and service offerings that may be of benefit to you. Please know that you can opt-out of any correspondence with our company or any of our trusted third-party partners at any time in the future; 

If you enter a contest or other promotion offered on an BackLinksGenie Site, we may, under the rules of the promotion, use your name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion; 

BackLinksGenie may also use Personal Information if it has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of a federal, provincial/state or foreign law or in order to protect or defend a legal interest. 

DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION We will only disclose your Personal Information to third parties: 

Where you have specifically opted in or agreed to receive email offers from Naughty Dog and/or its partners; 

As required by law, including by an order of any court, institution or body with jurisdiction or authority to compel the production of information, or in order to protect or defend a legal interest; or 

In connection with an BackLinksGenie corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of BackLinksGenie provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS A BackLinksGenie Service may contain links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the BackLinksGenie Services referencing this Privacy Policy. 

SECURITY The security of your Personal Information is important to us. BackLinksGenie takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your Personal Information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY BackLinksGenie may from time to time change its Privacy Policy as new BackLinksGenie Services are added or old ones changed. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted at an BackLinksGenie Site. Please check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates by checking the date of "Effective Date" at the top of this document. 

ADDITIONAL PRIVACY PROCEDURES Privacy procedures specific to an BackLinksGenie Service can be found on an BackLinksGenie Site at the location of the particular BackLinksGenie Service, or in additional terms referenced at such BackLinksGenie Site. Those procedures are an addendum to this policy, and are provided to you at the place where they will be of most use and relevance to you. 

If you decide at any time that you do not want to receive any e-mail materials to which you have subscribed, you may choose to unsubscribe to these e-mails from BackLinksGenie by following the instructions at the bottom of the e-mail material. 

Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
